thestupidstation.com 2014-11-03

# The Stupid Station - Stupidity must Live!

This privacy policy sets out how www.theStupidStation.com uses and protects any information that you give www.theStupidStation.com when you use this website. www.theStupidStation.com is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. www.theStupidStation.com may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from August, 2012. 

### What we collect

We may collect the following information:

  * Demographic information such as preferences, location, age and interests

  * Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

### What we do with the information we gather

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping.

  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.

  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided. 

  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests. 

### Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

### How we use cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website. 

### Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question. 

### Controlling your personal information

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  * Whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes 

  * if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by  **writing to us** **.**

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please  **contact us** on info@theStupidStation.com. If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect. 

#### Terms & Conditions

## Copyright & DMCA Guidelines

The following may be interpreted as The Stupid Station's (hereafter 'the Service') policy towards copyright infringement on the Service in accordance with the Digital Millenium Copyright Act (hereafter 'DMCA'). The address of The Stupid Station' Designated Agent for copyright takedown notices ('Designated Agent') is listed below.

### Reporting Instances of Infringement

If you believe copyright infringing Content is on or accessible through the Service, please send a notice of infringement of copyright containing the following information to the Designated Agent at the address listed below:

  * Identify the material or work being infringed.
  * Identify the material that is claimed to be infringing. This includes its location and enough detail so The Stupid Station will be able to accurately locate it.
  * Contact information for the notifying party.
  * A statement that the Notifying party has a good faith belief that the material is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent or law.
  * A statement made under penalty of perjury that the information provided is accurate and that the Notifying Party is authorized to make the complaint on behalf of the copyright owner.
  * A signature of the person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of the copyright, or the owner of the copyright that has been allegedly infringed.

After The Stupid Station removes material persuant to the DMCA notice, The Stupid Station will notify the user responsible for uploading the material that access to said material has been revoked. The Stupid Station reserves the right to immediately and without prior notification terminate accounts on the Service for copyright infringement, especially those which are the subject of repeat DMCA notifications.

### How To Submit a DMCA Counter-Notification

You may file a counter-notification to The Stupid Station if you believe material you have submitted to the Service has been the wrongful subject of a DMCA notification. Please provide the following information to the Designated Agent, listed below:

  * Specific URLs which refer to the material which was removed or to which access has been disabled.
  * Your name, address, telephone number, and email address.
  * You must include a statement consenting to the jurisdiction of Federal District Court for the judicial district in which your address is located (or the federal district courts located in San Francisco County, California if you are located outside of the United States). You must further agree to accept service of process from the original DMCA complaintant or the agent(s) of the original complaintant.
  * You must also swear under penalty of perjury that you have a good-faith belief that the material in question was removed or access to the material was disabled only as a result of a mistake or misidentification.

#### Send us a message now!

If you have any questions, suggestions or issues regarding the website or its content, you can send us a meesage by filling the below form anytime. We would be happy to assit you. :)
